For my next trick,
notice I have nothing up my sleeves
and nothing in my head.
So, if my lovely assistant
will kindly supply me
with an ordinary,
non-fake pitcher of milk...
Behold! The milk has vanished.
Exiled, perhaps, to another dimension.
Amazing.
That's why they call you
Bender the Magnificent.
No, it isn't.
Whoa.
They discovered an intact
20th-century pizzeria,
just like the one I used to work at.
Interesting.
No, wait, the other thing.
Tedious.
Let's go check it out.
You can see how I lived before I met you.
You lived before you met me?
Sure, lots of people did.
Really?
Truly, they were as gods,
who built this place.
Next,
we come to the splendidly preserved
wooden pizza paddle.
Scientists theorize
it was used to gently
discipline the delivery boy.
Wait a second.
This is Panucci's.
I used to work in this exact pizzeria.
And for your information, lady,
this was not just used to paddle my butt.
It was also used to move pizzas
and crush rats.
I don't know
where you get your facts, sir,
but I am a volunteer housewife
with 45 minutes of orientation
and a Harlequin romance
about archaeologists.
Don't wave your fancy degrees at me.
I recognize all this stuff.
Petrified sausages,
old Mr. Vitelli,
and that's...
Yes?
Pizza delivery for a Mr...
Seymour Asses.
There's no one by that name here.
Or anywhere.
I hope that in time
you'll realize what an idiot you've been.
I wouldn't count on that.
Aw. Poor little guy.
You look like
you haven't eaten in a month.
Here.
But if Mr. Panucci asks,
your name is Seymour Asses.
I like you, Seymour.
You're not constantly judging me
like all the other dogs.
Are you?
Nah. We understand each other.
People think you're just
a dumb mutt who smells bad,
can't find a girlfriend
and has a crummy job.
But you're keeping it real
and you call no man "mister."
Well, goodbye.
Live long and prosper.
Blech.
That's the least appetizing
calzone I've ever seen.
No, that's my dog in there.
It's an outrage, I say.
Hey...
Ow.
I'm taking him home and I'd like to see
anyone try and stop me. Uh-oh.
And then he was ejected by the guards.
Needless to say, I was mortified.
Well, it's not right to make
my dead pet an exhibit.
That's like digging up Lassie
and putting her on display in the Louvre.
Lassie is on display in the Louvre.
I know.
I was deliberately describing
a similar situation.
Why don't you try protesting?
Like those native Martians.
Always whining that people don't treat
their ancestors bones with respect.
Eh, protesting never works.
You're right.
I'll give it a shot.
What do you want?
Fry's dog!
When do you want it?
I will now perform
my people's native dance.
Do the Hustle...
It says here that this part of The Hustle
implores the gods to grant a favor,
usually a Trans Am.
I'm walking on sunshine, oh-oh
I'm walking on sunshine, whoa-oh
That-a-boy, Seymour.
Right here waiting for me as always.
Just like that huge mushroom in my shower.
Hey, there's our little mascot.
Aw, you've been swimming
in the sewer again?
You rascal.
Fry, clean up.
Seymour, clean up.
Good dog.
That's a good Seymour.
Yo, there's dog fur on my slice.
Nah, that's vermicelli.
No fur in here.
He's so cute.
He can do two things at one time,
eat and swim.
Ooh, three things.
Fry, it's been three days.
You can't keep boogying like this.
You'll come down with a fever
of some sort.
Mr. Fry, I'm Dr. Ben Beeler,
the paleontologist
who discovered your dog,
or as some call it, the Beelersaurus.
So do I get Seymour back?
Are you caving to political pressure?
No. We're sorry,
but there's just
too much that fossil can teach us
about dogs from your time.
His name was Seymour.
He was once intimate with the leg
of a wandering saxophonist.
He had wet dog smell,even when dry.
And he was not above chasing
the Number 29 bus.
The 29? Interesting.
- That's all I needed. Ray?
- I'm good.
Okay, then, here's your dog back.
Seymour!
Lady and gentleman,
how about a hand for my
temporary replacement assistant!
I was all in this part.
It's magic.
You're not fit to wear Fry's leotard!
Stop!
Good news, everyone.
Hooray, he's back!
And he's looking
for a garbage can to put the rock in.
Here you go, buddy.
No, actually we've discovered
that Fry's dog was fast-fossilized,
preserving its cellular structure.
Which means we can clone it.
Seymour will live again!
A little land mammal.
Can you believe it, Bender?
I'm going to havemy best friend back.
Why the idiot convention?
Ah, Cubert, my precious babe.
I'm going to attempt to clone Fry's dog
using the very same apparatus
I used to clone you.
Ooh, look.
There's a smidge of toe still in here.
You see, beneath the fossil's
crunchy mineral shell,
there's still a creamy core of dog nougat.
So will Seymour remember
how to sing Walking on Sunshine?
Amazingly, yes.
In cases of rapid fossilization,
I can press this brain-scan button,
retrieving Seymour's memories
at the precise instant of doggy death.
I'm going to get my puppy back.
In your face, Grim Reaper!
Crappy, ineffective reaper.
I just need to reset
the Clone-o-Mat from human mode
to dog mode.
The dog says...
Oh-oh, this may take a while.
You stink, loser!
Hey, Fry, pizza going out.
Come on!
But I'm celebrating New Year's Eve.
Like you got squat to celebrate.
You're a delivery boy this millennium
and you'll be a delivery boy
next millennium.
What's with Seymour?
It's like he don't want you to go
or he thinks your pants
is too short or something,
which is crazy,
because frankly, you look fabulous.
Now get going!
I won't be gone long, Seymour.
Just wait here till I come back.
Hello, pizza delivery for...
Aw, crud.
Here's to another lousy millennium.
Five, four,
three, two...
What the...
A dog collar for me?
You shouldn't have.
That's for Seymour.
Oh.
Say, why'd you get me
a subscription to the Daily Growl?
That's not a reputable journal of opinion.
Oh, that's also for Seymour.
I'm getting everything
ready for when he's cloned.
Are you on the junk, Fry?
Why are you wasting time
on a creature of inferior intelligence?
Hey, he was smart.He could fetch.
I can fetch.
He could dig up bones.
Hello. Charlemagne?
Plus, I bet he couldn't create
a laser show with his head.
Look, Bender,
this has nothing to do with you.
That's impossible!
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm working on Seymour's doghouse.
No one ever asks if Bender
would like to live
in a tiny little house.
Not that I would.
A tiny little house
that says "Bender" on it.
Ow!
This is Fry.
If you're calling
about the used towels for sale,
they're still available for $45 each.
Phil, it's your father. Where are you?
You're holding up New Year's brunch.
Your brother can't wait any longer.
Hello, first bologna
of the new millennium.
Ah, here he comes.
That's him and Seymour.
Well, that's weird.
Seymour's here, but...
Go! Go! Touchdown!
But where's Philip?
I'm telling you,
the Y2K computer's got him.
We'll face burning roads,
rivers exploding,
calculators transformed
into Scud missiles.
There's nothing we can do.
What's that, Seymour?
You walking on sunshine?
He's trying to tell us something.
Maybe he can lead us to Philip.
Should we follow him?
To our deaths? Negatory.
It's the Y2K trying to lure us
into an ambush, and I ain't buying it.
Pass the bologna.
Are you two going to be done soon?
Sorry, but we need to practice
hand-to-hand combat
in case an enemy knocks the laser guns
out of our hands
and they slide way across the room.
Well, could you do it someplace else?
I'm setting up Seymour'sdoggie bed.
- Okay.
- Ow!
Heel, boy, heel.
Oh, hello, Fry.
I guess I didn't notice you there.
I'm having such fun
with my new best friend,
Robo-Puppy.
That's nice.
I was just out walking him.
Yes, you can walk him.
Of course, after he goes,
you have to refill the canisters.
Come here, boy. Pet, pet, pet.
Robo-Puppy receiving petting.
Bender, are you jealous of Fry's puppy?
That's so adorable.
Jealous? Not when I have
the love of Robo-Puppy here.
Robo-Puppy, lick my cheek.
Robo-Puppy preparing to lick cheek.
Robo-Puppy commencing cheek licking.
Licking in progress.
Licking complete.
Robo-Puppy truly is
robot's best friend, huh?
Ah! There, perfect.
Good news, everyone.
The Clone-o-Mat is ready!
Finally.
Robo-Puppy commencing
two hour yipping session.
Robo-Puppy mistreatment alert!
Behold once more, the mighty Clone-o-Mat.
Requiring such vast amounts
of electricity that we must
harness the elemental power
of nature itself.
I speak, of course,
of molten lava deep within
the Earth's core.
To the subbasement.
Powering up Clone-o-Mat.
Placing fossil on the plat-clone-o-form.
Initiating dog brain CAT scan.
Come on, boy, come back to life.
Know ye now what it feels like
to be Dog God.
Commencing DNA extraction.
Fry, come on, the talent show.
What? I'm in the middle of something.
But if we don't perform,
in what sense do we have an act?
Bender, enough. Leave me alone.
So that's how it is, huh?
I thought you were my friend,
but if you love your dog so much
maybe you'd rather play fetch.
No!
Now I'm all you got.
I hate you!
I hate you, you evil metal man!
Ow!
So anyway, your dog is melted.
Now we're friends again.
Not necessarily,
for the dog may yet survive.
May yet? Really?
Indeed.
You see, that fossilwas made of dolomite,
the tough black mineralthat won't cop out
when there's heat all about.
By contrast, observe the lava's effect
on this ice swan.
Of course, that would have melted
even at room temperature.
I just wanted to get rid of it.
But had it been made of that
righteous mineral dolomite,
there's a slim chance
it might have survived.
So Seymour might still exist?
Perhaps, for a few minutes.
It's dolomite, baby.
Then I'm going in after him.
He'd come after me.
Acting like a moron
won't bring your dog back.
Then all hope is lost.
Goodbye, Seymour.
Please stop crying, Fry.
Here.
I assumed you were just pretending
to love the dog
to toy with my emotions.
Oh, what have I done?
You didn't do anything.
Don't beat yourself up.
Fry, I'm sorry.
I should have understood
how someone can love
an inferior creature, because I love you.
Not in the way of the ancient Greeks,
but the way a robot loves a human,
a human loves a dog,
and, occasionally,
a gorilla loves a kitty.
I'm going in.
I'm a professor.
Why isn't anyone listening to me?
You can't go in because you'll melt.
The fossil only has a chance
because it's made of dolomite.
I'm 40% dolomite.
Oh, it's hot. Oh, it's very hot.
Oh, I am one hungover cryogenicist.
Just throw that mutt in the freezer
till his owners get here.
You can't solve all your problems
by freezing them, boss.
I think you're forgetting our motto.
Are you the cryogenicist
who called about our son's dog?
Oh! You must be the Frys.
Yeah, he's right over there.
Sorry we're late.
We all got sickfrom eating bad bologna.
Y2K.
What's he so worked up about?
He's just upset'cause our boy's missing.
Come on, you overgrown rat,
lead us to Philip.
Bender's been down there too long.
I'm going in after him.
Professor! Lava! Hot!
This is all my fault.
I let my best friend risk his life
just to get my dead dog back.
Bender!
And that is why they call me
Bender the Magnificent.
Hey, where'd everybody go?
- Okay, let's clone us some dog.
- Yeah!
Very well...
Let this abomination unto the Lord begin!
Interesting.
It seems Seymour died
at the ripe old age of 15.
Fifteen?
You mean, he lived for 12 more years
after I got frozen?
Indeed.
Stop the cloning.
Oh, sure,smash the smart guy's machine.
Fry, what's wrong?
Think about it.
Seymour lived a full life
after I was gone.
He probably even added
new songs to his repertoire.
But that's a good thing.
Walking on Sunshine sucks noodles.
I had Seymour till he was three.
That's when I knew him,
and that's when I loved him.
I'll never forget him.
But he forgot me a long, long time ago.
If it takes forever
I will wait for you
For a thousand summers
Till you're back beside me
Till I'm holding you
Till I hear you sigh
Here in my arms...
Ow!
If it takes forever
I will wait for you
For a thousand summers
I will wait for you...